See, Deepanshu, the stock that Rakesh and I have chosen today in Earnings 10
is
ICICI Lombard, in which we have
seen a big action today. We had
recommended insurance companies before also,
we had recommended GIC RE. A
tremendous rally was seen at the lower levels.
Rakesh and I
gave a buy opinion on LIC in Earnings 10, and today you can see that
new highs are being formed in LIC,
and now our buy opinion is on
ICICI Lombard, in which we feel
that it should be amortized in the medium to long term. The
stock is definitely in the F end, but
if you look at it overall, then buy it
in the cash market. Buy for the medium to long term. The
stock has
not shown that kind of performance, but we feel
that it is a safe buy at these levels, so
amortize in case of decline at the current levels.
Over
to Deepanshu, there is an excellent technical structure, it is
running around 1430-35. If the
stock ever gets around 1377-1375 in correction, then it will be
golden.  The levels are 1650, our
target is 1650, this is our
investment advice in ICICI Lombard,
this is for you, ICICI Lombard is the one
you have to keep an eye on, insurance stocks in fact
across the board, all the insurance
stocks, you should also
get this another interesting news on your
screen.